{
    "subject": "resource/Lasse_M\u00e5rtenson",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Lasse Martenson",
    "human_readable": "The full name of Lasse M\u00e5rtenson is Lasse Martenson.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9797857403755188,
            "question": "What is the full name of Lasse M\u00e5rtenson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9644280672073364,
            "question": "Is 'Lasse Martenson' a shortened version of someone's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9305861592292786,
            "question": "What is the last name of Lasse M\u00e5rtenson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9233556985855103,
            "question": "Is there a connection between 'Lasse M\u00e5rtenson' and 'Lasse Martenson'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9054473042488098,
            "question": "How many names are included in Lasse M\u00e5rtenson's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8985442519187927,
            "question": "Does Lasse M\u00e5rtenson's full name contain two words?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8912575840950012,
            "question": "What is the first name of Lasse M\u00e5rtenson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8348731398582458,
            "question": "Could 'Lasse Martenson' be a stage name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7210732102394104,
            "question": "How might someone address Lasse M\u00e5rtenson formally?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6962082982063293,
            "question": "What does the hyphen in 'M\u00e5rtenson' suggest about his name?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The full name of Lasse M\u00e5rtenson is Lasse Martenson.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1369_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How might someone address Lasse M\u00e5rtenson formally?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1369_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could 'Lasse Martenson' be a stage name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1369_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the first name of Lasse M\u00e5rtenson?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1369_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1369_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1369_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1369_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1369_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1369_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1369_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1369_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1369_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1369_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1369_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'} \n\n\n**Explanation:**\n\nThe documents state that the full name of Lasse M\u00e5rtenson is \"Lars Anders Fredrik\".  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe correct answer is no because the documents mention that Lasse M\u00e5rtenson's birth name was Lars Anders Fredrik \"Lasse\" M\u00e5rtenson, not Lasse Martenson."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nThe provided documents state that the full name of Lasse M\u00e5rtenson is \"M\u00e5rtenson, Lars Anders Fredrik\" or commonly known as \"Lasse M\u00e5rtenson\". Therefore, the statement that his full name is simply \"Lasse Martenson\" without the correct spelling and additional names is incorrect."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}